Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records 1954-2010 IBT0053
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1984, June 12-14 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, August 7 (Box 126, Folder 2)
- Council Meeting, 1984, September 10 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1984, September 11 (Box 126, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1984, September 11-12 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1984, September 11-12 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1984, September 11-12 (Box 126, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1984, September 11-12 (Box 126, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1984, September 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1984, December 10 (Box 127, Folder 2)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1984, December 11 (Box 127, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1984, December 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1984, December 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1984, December 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1984, December 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1984, December 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1984, December 11-12 (Box 127, Folder 9)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, December 27 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, December 27 (Box 128, Folder 2)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, December 27 (Box 128, Folder 3)
- Local and Short Haul Committee Meeting, 1984, December 27 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- Union Rider Committee Meeting, 1984, December 27 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- Central States Maintenance Meeting, 1985, February 7 (Box 128, Folder 6)
- Special Meeting, 1985, April 19 (Box 128, Folder 7)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1985, April 29 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1985, April 30 (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1985, April 30 (Box 128, Folder 10)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1985, April 30 & May 1 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1985, April 30 & May 1 (Box 128, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1985, April 30 & May 1 (Box 128, Folder 13)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1985, April 30 & May 1 (Box 128, Folder 14)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1985, June 10 (Box 128, Folder 15)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1985, June 11 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1985, June 11-12 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1985, June 11-12 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Comittee Meeting, 1985, June 11-12 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1985, June 11-12 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1985, June 11-12 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1985, June 11-12 (Box 129, Folder 7)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1985, September 9 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1985, September 10 (Box 129, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1985, September 10-11 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1985, September 10-11 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1985, September 10-11 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1985, September 10-11 (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1985, September 10-11 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1985, September 10-11 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1985, September 12 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1985, September 12 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Special Hearing Meeting, 1985, Sepember 12 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Union Review Committee Meeting, 1985, September 12 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1985, December 9 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1985, December 10 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1985, December 10-11 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1985, December 10-11 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1985, December 10-11 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1985, December 10-11 (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1985, December 10-11 (Box 131, Folder 10)
- Negotiating Committee Meeting, 1985, December 12 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1986, February 7 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1986, March 10 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- Freight Conference Meeting, 1986, March 10 (Box 132, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1986, March 11 (Box 132, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1986, March 11 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, March 11-12 (Box 132, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, March 11-12 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1986, March 11-12 (Box 132, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1986, March 12 (Box 132, Folder 10)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1986, June 9 (Box 132, Folder 11)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1986, June 10 (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, June 10-11 (Box 133, Folder 8)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1986, August 19 (Box 133, Folder 9)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1986, September 8 (Box 133, Folder 10)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1986, September 9 (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, September 9-10 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, September 9-10 (Box 134, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1986, September 9-10 (Box 134, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1986, September 9-10 (Box 134, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, September 9-10 (Box 134, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, September 9-10 (Box 134, Folder 7)
- Deadlocked Case Meeting, 1986, September 10 (Box 134, Folder 8)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1986, September 11 (Box 134, Folder 9)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1986, September 11 (Box 134, Folder 10)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1986, December 8 (Box 135, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1986, December 9 (Box 135, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, December 9-10 (Box 135, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, December 9-10 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1986, December 9-10 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1986, December 9-10 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1986, December 9-10 (Box 135, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1986, December 9-10 (Box 135, Folder 8)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1986, December 11 (Box 136, Folder 1)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1987, March 9 (Box 136, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1987, March 10 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1987, March 10-11 (Box 136, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1987, March 10-11 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1987, March 10-11 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1987, March 11 (Box 136, Folder 7)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1987, May 22 (Box 136, Folder 8)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1987, June 8 (Box 136, Folder 9)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1987, June 9 (Box 136, Folder 10)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1987, June 9 (Box 136, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1987, June 9-10 (Box 137, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1987, June 9-10 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1987, June 9-10 (Box 137, Folder 3)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1987, July 15 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1987, September 21 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1987, September 21 (Box 137, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1987, September 22 (Box 137, Folder 7)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1987, September 22 (Box 137, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1987, September 22 (Box 137, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1987, September 22 (Box 137, Folder 10)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1987, September 22-23 (Box 138, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1987, September 23 (Box 138, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1987, December 14 (Box 138, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1987, December 15 (Box 138, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1987, December 15 (Box 138, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1987, December 15 (Box 138, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1987, December 15 (Box 138, Folder 7)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 8)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 9)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 10)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 11)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 12)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 13)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 14)
- Grievance Subcommittee Meeting, 1987, December 29 (Box 138, Folder 15)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1988, June 13 (Box 138, Folder 16)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, June 14 (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, June 14 (Box 139, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1988, June 14-15 (Box 139, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, June 14-15 (Box 139, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, June 14-15 (Box 139, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, June 14-15 (Box 139, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, June 14-15 (Box 139, Folder 7)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1988, June 15 (Box 139, Folder 8)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1988, June 16 (Box 139, Folder 9)
- Special Committee Meeting, 1988, July 18 (Box 139, Folder 10)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1988, September 12 (Box 140, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, September 13-14 (Box 140, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, September 13-14 (Box 140, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1988, September 13-14 (Box 140, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1988, September 13-14 (Box 140, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, September 13-14 (Box 140, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, September 13-14 (Box 140, Folder 7)
- Negotiating Committee Meeting, 1988, September 14 (Box 140, Folder 8)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1988, September 15 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1988, September 15 (Box 141, Folder 2)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1988, September 15 (Box 141, Folder 3)
- Special Freight Division Meeting, 1988, September 15 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1988, December 12 (Box 141, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1988, December 13 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1988, December 13-14 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, December 13-14 (Box 141, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, December 13-14 (Box 141, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1988, December 13-14 (Box 141, Folder 10)
- Over-the-Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1988, December 13-14 (Box 141, Folder 11)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1988, December 14 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1988, December 15 (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1989, March 13 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1989, March 14-15 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1989, March 14-15 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1989, March 14-15 (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1989, March 14-15 (Box 142, Folder 7)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1989, March 16 (Box 142, Folder 8)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1990, September 10 (Box 142, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1990, September 11-12 (Box 142, Folder 10)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1990, September 11-12 (Box 142, Folder 11)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1990, September 11-12 (Box 142, Folder 12)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1990, September 11-12 (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1990, September 11-12 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1990, September 12 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1990, December 10 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1990, December 11-12 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1990, December 11-12 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1990, December 11-12 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1990, December 11-12 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1990, December 11-12 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1990, December 12 (Box 144, Folder 2)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1990, December 12 (Box 144, Folder 3)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1990, December 12 (Box 144, Folder 4)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1991, March 25 (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1991, March 26 (Box 144, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1991, March 26-27 (Box 144, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1991, March 26-27 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1991, March 26-27 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- National Grievance Committee Meeting, 1991, June 16 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1991, July 16 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1991, July 17-18 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1991, July 17-18 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1991, July 18 (Box 145, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1991, July 18 (Box 145, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1991, July 18 (Box 145, Folder 7)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1991, September 9 (Box 145, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1991, September 10-11 (Box 145, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1991, September 10-11 (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1991, September 10-11 (Box 146, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1991, September 10-11 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1991, September 10-11 (Box 146, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1991, September 10-11 (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Council Meeting, 1991, December 9 (Box 146, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1991, December 10 (Box 146, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1991, December 10 (Box 147, Folder 1)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1991, December 10 (Box 147, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1991, December 10-11 (Box 147, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1991, December 10-11 (Box 147, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1991, December 10-11 (Box 147, Folder 5)
- Conference Committee Meeting, 1991, December 10-11 (Box 147, Folder 6)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1992, March 9 (Box 147, Folder 7)
- Union Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1992, March 10 (Box 147, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, March 10-11 (Box 148, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, March 10-11 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, March 10-11 (Box 148, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, March 10-11 (Box 148, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, March 10-11 (Box 148, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, March 10-11 (Box 148, Folder 6)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1992, March 11 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Special Circumstances Cases Meeting, 1992, March 11 (Box 149, Folder 2)
- Alcohol and Drug Committee Meeting, 1992, March 11 (Box 149, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1992, June 8 (Box 149, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1992, June 9 (Box 149, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, June 9-10 (Box 149, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, June 9-10 (Box 149, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, June 9-10 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, June 9-10 (Box 150, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1992, June 9-10 (Box 150, Folder 3)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1992, June 10 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1992, June 10 (Box 150, Folder 5)
- Rules of Procedure Committee Meeting, 1992, June 10 (Box 150, Folder 6)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, July 14 (Box 150, Folder 7)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, July 14 (Box 150, Folder 8)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1992, September 14 (Box 151, Folder 1)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1992, September 14 (Box 151, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1992, September 15-16 (Box 151, Folder 3)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1992, September 15-16 (Box 151, Folder 4)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, September 15-16 (Box 151, Folder 5)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, September 15-16 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- Drug Committee Conference Meeting, 1992, September 15-16 (Box 151, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1992, September 15-16 (Box 151, Folder 8)
- Article VI Committee Meeting, 1992, September 16 (Box 151, Folder 9)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1992, September 16 (Box 151, Folder 10)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1992, September 16 (Box 152, Folder 1)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1992, September 16 (Box 152, Folder 2)
- Special Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1992, September 24 (Box 152, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1992, December 14 (Box 152, Folder 4)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1992, December 15-16 (Box 152, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1992, December 15-16 (Box 152, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, December 15-16 (Box 152, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, December 15-16 (Box 152, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1992, December 15-16 (Box 152, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1992, December 15-16 (Box 153, Folder 1)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1992, December 16 (Box 153, Folder 2)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1992, December 16 (Box 153, Folder 3)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1992, December 16 (Box 153, Folder 4)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1992, December 16 (Box 153, Folder 5)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1993, March (Box 153, Folder 6)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1993, March 8 (Box 153, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1993, March 9-10 (Box 153, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1993, March 9-10 (Box 153, Folder 9)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1993, March 9-10 (Box 153, Folder 10)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1993, March 9-10 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1993, March 10 (Box 154, Folder 2)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1993, June 14 (Box 154, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1993, June 15-16 (Box 154, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1993, June 15-16 (Box 154, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1993, June 15-16 (Box 154, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1993, June 15-16 (Box 154, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1993, June 15-16 (Box 155, Folder 1)
- Alcohol and Drug Committee Meeting, 1993, June 16 (Box 155, Folder 2)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1993, June 16 (Box 155, Folder 3)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1993, September 13 (Box 155, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1993, September 14-15 (Box 155, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1993, September 14-15 (Box 155, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1993, September 14-15 (Box 155, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1993, September 14-15 (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1993, September 14-15 (Box 156, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1993, September 14-15 (Box 156, Folder 3)
- Alcohol and Drug Committee Meeting, 1993, September 15 (Box 156, Folder 4)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1993, September 15 (Box 156, Folder 5)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1993, December 13 (Box 156, Folder 6)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1993, December 14 (Box 156, Folder 7)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1993, December 14-15 (Box 156, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1993, December 14-15 (Box 156, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1993, December 14-15 (Box 157, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1993, December 14-15 (Box 157, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1993, December 14-15 (Box 157, Folder 3)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1993, December 15 (Box 157, Folder 4)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1993, December 15 (Box 157, Folder 5)
- Freight Division Meeting, 1994, March 14 (Box 157, Folder 6)
- Alcohol and Drug Committee Meeting, 1994, March 15 (Box 157, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1994, March 15-16 (Box 158, Folder 1)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1994, March 15-16 (Box 158, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1994, March 15-16 (Box 158, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1994, March 15-16 (Box 158, Folder 4)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1994, March 16 (Box 158, Folder 5)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1994, May 19 (Box 158, Folder 6)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1994, May 19 (Box 158, Folder 7)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1994, May 19 (Box 158, Folder 8)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1994, May 19 (Box 158, Folder 9)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1994, May 19 (Box 158, Folder 10)
- Grievance Hearing Meeting, 1994, May 20 (Box 158, Folder 11)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1994, June 14 (Box 158, Folder 12)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1994, June 14-15 (Box 158, Folder 13)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1994, June 14-15 (Box 158, Folder 14)
- Union Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1994, June 14-15 (Box 158, Folder 15)